A Guide to the Publicity Photographs of U. S. Senator Hugh Scott, 1958-1973
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- 1971 December 17 Senator Scott with a Senate page (139c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 December 17 Senator Scott with a Senate page (139d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1972 January 14 Campaign portrait with flag and pipe (139e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1972 January 14 Campaign portrait with flag and pipe (139f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 Scott smoking pipe with flag in background (copied from color slide) (140a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1971 Scott smoking pipe with flag in background (copied from color slide) (140b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1973 December Senator Scott at dinner table, chatting with Dwight D. Eisenhower (140c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1973 December Senator Scott at dinner table, chatting with Dwight D. Eisenhower (140d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1972 January 14 Campaign portrait with flag and pipe (141a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1972 January 14 Campaign portrait with flag and pipe (141b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1972 January 14 Campaign portrait with flag and pipe (141c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1972 January 20 Senator Hugh Scott during a press conference, informal (candid) (141d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1972 January 20 Senator Hugh Scott during a press conference, informal (candid) (141e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1972 January 20 Senator Hugh Scott during a press conference, informal (candid) (141f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1972 January 20 Senator Hugh Scott during a press conference, informal (candid) (141g) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1972 January 20 Scott during a press conference, informal (candid) (142a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1972 January 20 Scott embracing his wife (copied) (142b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1972 Senator and Mrs. Scott relaxing with their cat in their Washington DC home (142c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1972 Senator and Mrs. Scott relaxing with their cat in their Washington DC home (142d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1973 April 5 Scott practicing writing his name with Chinese figures (142e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1973 July 30 Portrait of Senator Scott, drawing by Louis Lupas (142f) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1973 July 30 Portrait of Senator Scott, drawing by Louis Lupas (143a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1973 July 30 Portrait of Senator Scott, drawing by Louis Lupas (143b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1973 July 30 Portrait of Senator Scott, drawing by Louis Lupas (143c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1973 July 30 Portrait of Senator Scott, drawing by Louis Lupas (143d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1973 July 30 Portrait of Senator Scott, drawing by Louis Lupas (143e) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1973 December Scott working in Republican Leader's office of US Capital on new book of Chinese antiquities (144a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1973 December Scott working in Republican Leader's office of US Capital on new book of Chinese antiquities (144b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1973 December Scott working in Republican Leader's office of US Capital on new book of Chinese antiquities (144c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1973 Headshot of Scott with pipe, copied from a color photo (145a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1973 Headshot of Scott with pipe, copied from a color photo (145b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1974 August 23 Senator Barry Goldwater, Senator Hugh Scott, Representative John J. Rhodes leave White House meeting with President Nixon, discussing his lack of Congressional support (photo by Charles Del Vecchio of The Washington Post) (145c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1974 August 23 Senator Barry Goldwater, Senator Hugh Scott, Representative John J. Rhodes leave White House meeting with President Nixon, discussing his lack of Congressional support (photo by Charles Del Vecchio of The Washington Post) (145d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1974 August 23 Senator Barry Goldwater, Senator Hugh Scott, Representative John J. Rhodes leave White House meeting with President Nixon, White House Press conference on lawn (photo by White House Press) (146a) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1974 August 23 Senator Barry Goldwater, Senator Hugh Scott, Representative John J. Rhodes leave White House meeting with President Nixon, White House Press conference on lawn (photo by White House Press) (146b) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1974 August Scott at Russian conference (146c) (Box-folder 1:4)
- 1974 August Scott at Russian conference (146d) (Box-folder 1:4)
- n.d. Headshot of Scott (147a) (Box-folder 1:4)